<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><propertyList date="01-02-2024:20:39" username="enquiries@smartsalesbroker.com.au" password="sam@johmar.com.au1"><business modTime="2024-02-01" status="current">
<agentID>2921</agentID>
<uniqueID>357732</uniqueID>
<commercialListingType value="sale" />
<underOffer value="no" />
<listingAgent>
    <name>JBS</name>
    <telephone type="BH">1300 889 443</telephone>
    <email>enquiry.johmar@gmail.com</email>
</listingAgent>
<price display="yes" plusSAV="no">230000</price>
<priceView><![CDATA[From $230-290k]]></priceView>
<netProfit period="annual"></netProfit>
<address display="No">
<streetNumber>357732/7534</streetNumber>
<street><![CDATA[abc street]]></street>
<suburb display="Yes">North Sydney</suburb>
<state>NSW</state>
<postcode>2060</postcode>
<country>AUS</country>
</address>
<businessCategory id="1"><name>Retail</name>
<businessSubCategory><name>Food/Beverage</name></businessSubCategory>
</businessCategory>
<businessCategory id="2"><name>Food/Hospitality</name>
<businessSubCategory><name>Takeaway Food</name></businessSubCategory>
</businessCategory>
<businessCategory id="3"><name>Franchise</name>
<businessSubCategory><name>Franchise</name></businessSubCategory>
</businessCategory>
<headline><![CDATA[Graze Craze Food Franchise For Sale – Grazing Board/Charcuterie – Locations Across Sydney – Takeout/Delivery/Catering – Training – No Cooking]]></headline>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Franchise Fee: $64,500</strong></p>

<p><strong>Royalties: 6%</strong></p>

<p><strong>Total Investment: from $170,000 (includes franchise fee)</strong></p>

<p><strong>JOIN THE GRAZE CRAZE! - A Food Trend with Staying Power. If you&rsquo;ve considered investing in a food franchise, this grazing board and charcuterie business is perfect for you. Graze Craze has already developed steady followings in each community it serves and is looking to expand to new locations throughout Sydney. The charcuterie board business is a part of the franchise powerhouse, United Franchise Group. Graze Craze offers takeout, delivery, and catering, which means no cooking or greasy vents. The easy-to-run franchise comes with the advantages of low-investment, full training, and site selection and development. Thus, driven individuals can fulfil their entrepreneurial dreams by acquiring a Graze Craze location.&nbsp;</strong></p>

<p>The charcuterie board offers an assortment of cured meats, cheeses, artisan breads, olives, fruits, vegetables and desserts. A Graze Craze food experience includes a fully accessible concierge grade of customer service at a reasonable price. Nowadays, many customers have special dietary requirements that make it difficult for them to partake in the processed food sold at most restaurants. Charcuterie boards are meant to offer variety, so people can sample only the foods that work for them.&nbsp;<strong>And with fresh fruits, berries, nuts, and veggies as staples, these trays have something everyone can enjoy&mdash;opening up the pool of potential customers in your area.</strong></p>

<p><strong>The fast food and takeaway industry is worth an estimated $22bn in Australia. Add to this the rising popularity of grazing/charcuterie boards and you have an exciting new business in an industry primed for growth. It is the best way to become your own boss and start earning quickly.&nbsp;</strong></p>

<p><strong>Why Franchise with Graze Craze?</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>No cooking is required to make a winning charcuterie board&nbsp;</li>
	<li>No industrial kitchen equipment is needed, which reduces the initial investment&nbsp;</li>
	<li>Training provided to run, manage and promote a successful franchise</li>
	<li>A turnkey process that comes with everything you need to run the business&nbsp;</li>
	<li>The sale includes equipment, hardware, software, fixtures and furnishings</li>
	<li>Well-researched sites and assistance with lease negotiation and store build-out</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Graze Craze was founded in 2020 by a U.S. Airforce veteran who had spent years working in the food industry. The opportunity has now reached the Australian shores! So, don&rsquo;t miss out on this stunning proposition and call us TODAY!</strong></p>]]></description>
<objects>
<img id="m" modTime="2024-02-01-20:39:41" url="https://ik.imagekit.io/og2qfmlopB2S/tr:w-1200,h-1200,f-auto/1688350407_40lrg.jpg" format="jpg" />
<img id="a" modTime="2024-02-01-20:39:42" url="https://ik.imagekit.io/og2qfmlopB2S/tr:w-1200,h-1200,f-auto/1688350411_52lrg.png" format="jpg" />
<img id="b" modTime="2024-02-01-20:39:44" url="https://ik.imagekit.io/og2qfmlopB2S/tr:w-1200,h-1200,f-auto/1688350415_27lrg.jpg" format="jpg" />
<img id="c" modTime="2024-02-01-20:39:45" url="https://ik.imagekit.io/og2qfmlopB2S/tr:w-1200,h-1200,f-auto/1688350416_35lrg.jpg" format="jpg" />
<img id="d" modTime="2024-02-01-20:39:46" url="https://ik.imagekit.io/og2qfmlopB2S/tr:w-1200,h-1200,f-auto/1688350415_38lrg.jpg" format="jpg" />
<img id="e" modTime="2024-02-01-20:39:48" url="https://ik.imagekit.io/og2qfmlopB2S/tr:w-1200,h-1200,f-auto/1688350415_13lrg.jpg" format="jpg" />
<img id="f" modTime="2024-02-01-20:39:49" url="https://ik.imagekit.io/og2qfmlopB2S/tr:w-1200,h-1200,f-auto/1688350415_82lrg.jpg" format="jpg" />
<img id="g" modTime="2024-02-01-20:39:50" url="https://ik.imagekit.io/og2qfmlopB2S/tr:w-1200,h-1200,f-auto/1688350421_11lrg.jpeg" format="jpg" />
</objects>
</business>
</propertyList>